(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
そこに跪け
Kneel before me.
吐いて捨てるような現実は
A reality you'd spit out and throw away...
一刀両断叩き切る
I'll cut it down with a single stroke!
終わりなき因縁に惑いし凝らよ
To those of you lost in an endless cycle of fate...
漆黒の翼でいざなおう
I shall guide you with my jet-black wings.
我らエデンの星を統べるもの。秘密結社...
We are the rulers of Eden's Star. Secret Society...
holoX!
でござる
I'm here!
皆の者、かかれー！
Everyone, charge!
イエス・マイ・ダーク！
Yes, My Dark!
holoX 1周年!!
新メンバー登場!!
みんなでアイドル衣装ライブ
ユニットオリジナル楽曲
holoX 1st Anniversary!!
New member appearance!!
Everyone in idol costumes live
Unit original song
はい、ということでやっぱりラプラスが口上やらないと締まらないな
Right, it just doesn't feel right without La+ doing the intro spiel.
ねー、真ん中いなかったですねー。
Yeah, the center was empty.
というわけでオープニングね、見ていただいた方気づいたと思いますが
So, for those who watched the opening, you might have noticed...
先ほどもね、Twitterでも報告がありました
...as we also reported on Twitter just now,
本日ね、ラプラスはちょっと体調不良でお休みとなり
La+ is taking the day off today due to feeling unwell,
私たち4人でやらせていただきますので、よろしくお願いいたします。
so the four of us will be hosting. We're counting on you!
お願いしまーす！
Nice to meet you!
おやすみー！ゆっくり休んでね！
Get well soon! Take a good rest!
いい子に寝てるんだぞ、わかったな！
Make sure you're being a good girl and sleeping, okay?
はい、じゃあね。ラプラスがホワイトボードにね、今回の配信の概要を書いてくれてるんで
Alright then. La+ wrote an outline of today's stream on the whiteboard,
みんな... え、ちょっと違うわ
so everyone... wait, that's not right.
え？大丈夫？大丈夫？大丈夫？
Huh? You okay? You okay?
ということでみんな集まってください
Anyway, everyone, gather around.
バレないように最初から間違えてます
She made a mistake right from the start to hide it.
ラプラスに任せると、ラプラスちゃんちょっと調子が悪いんでござる
Whenever we leave it to La+, she's always a bit off-kilter.
ルイルイに任せるみたいな流れがいつもあるからねー
It always ends up being left to Lui-lui.
はい、ということで私たちの目標は何ですか、皆さん？
Right, so, what are our goals, everyone?
えっと、2年目も頑張る！
Umm, let's do our best in our second year!
いっぱい寝る！
Sleep a lot!
元気に過ごす！
Stay healthy!
え、それはみんなのね、目標ね
Uh, those are just your personal goals.
ホロックスとしての目標は何ですか？
What are our goals as holoX?
2年目も頑張る！
Do our best in our second year!
楽しむ！
Have fun!
健やかに生きる！
Live healthily!
ラプラスが後で見たら泣くよ
La+ is going to cry when she sees this later.
わかってます、それもそうなんだけど...
I know, I know that's true, but...
やはりね、ラプラスの目標は世界征服ですね。
After all, La+'s goal is world domination.
ああー。言ってるよねー。1年目からずっと言ってるね。
Ah. She has been saying that. She's been saying it since the first year.
そろそろやるんか？っていう感じだけど。本当にやるんか？ってね。
It's like, "Are you finally going to do it?" Like, "Are you really going to do it?"
というわけで今回もですね、世界征服に向けて前進をするために、
So, this time as well, in order to move forward towards world domination,
結構ね、魅力的なものを用意しておりますので！
we have prepared something quite attractive!
おおー！何だ何だ？
Oh! What is it, what is it?
刮目せよ！刮目せよ！
Behold! Behold!
はい、ということで、ホワイトボードをもう一回見てみましょう。
Alright, so let's take another look at the whiteboard.
まずは、ホロックス1周年おめでとう！
First of all, happy 1st anniversary to holoX!
もう1年経ったわけですけれども。今回ね、火漏れれ先生に...
It's been a year already. This time, Hiwa-sensei...
キービジュアルも作成していただきました。キービジュアル出るかな？どうぞ！
has created a key visual for us. Will the key visual appear? Here it is!
わあー！かっこいい！めっちゃかっこいい！
Wow! So cool! It's so cool!
この5人だったら世界征服できるよ！
With these five, we can definitely conquer the world!
確かに！これ世界征服してるでしょ、もう！
True! We've already conquered the world with this!
ラプラスも、すごいね、興興奮してたもんね。
La+ was really excited about it too, wasn't she?
ねー！嬉しかったねー！
Yeah! She was so happy!
お部屋にも飾ってあります。ラプちゃんのね、椅子の横に。
It's also displayed in the room. Right next to La-chan's chair.
良いね。おしゃれでござるな。
Nice. It's so stylish.
はい、ということでね、1年経ったということでね、ますますね...
Alright, so since it's been a year, even more so...
2年目も頑張っていきたい私たちなんですけれども、
we want to do our best in our second year as well,
なんと2年目にして新メンバーが登場いたします！
but surprisingly, in our second year, a new member will be appearing!
ええー！？ええー！？ついに来たんだ！七草目？
What!? What!? It's finally here! The 7th member?
それが気になってるっていう人もいたんですよ。
There were people who were curious about that.
ねー！え、七草目もホロックスに入れていく？
Yeah! Are we going to include the 7th member in holoX?
入れていく、入れていく！
We're including them, we're including them!
どんどん増やそうぜ！
Let's keep adding more!
何人来るのかもね、わからないからね。
We don't even know how many people are coming.
え、複数人！？大丈夫！？管理できるでござるか？
What, multiple people!? Is it okay!? Can we manage them?
誰の管理をする？ 管理はでもさ、ルイ姉に任せれば...
Who's going to manage them? Well, if we leave it to Lui-nee...
もういらない、もういらない！なんか、我々が十分新メンバー...
I don't need any more! I mean, we're already like new members ourselves...
今から出てくるのかわいそうでしょ！
It'll be pitiful for the one coming out now!
もう、じゃあ、手がかからない子でお願いします。
Well then, please let it be a child who doesn't need much care.
ああー、それは大事なのかな。手かかるかな？どうかな？
Ah, that might be important. Will they be a handful? I wonder.
ということで、何人来るかもお楽しみに！
So, look forward to seeing how many are coming!
続いて、実はね、みんな、もうアイドル衣装はお披露目していますけれども、
Next, actually, everyone has already revealed their idol outfits,
みんなでアイドル衣装ライブしてみたくない？
but don't you want to do an idol outfit live with everyone?
やってみたいー！やったー！
I want to do it! Yay!
ということで、みんなで集まってライブをしましょう、ということになります。
So, it means we'll all gather and have a live performance.
ついに！並びたいー！
Finally! I want to stand in line!
ついに5人揃って、アイドル衣装になってね、踊ったり歌ったりするので、
Finally, all five of us will be in idol outfits, dancing and singing,
皆さん楽しみにしててね！ワクワクだね！
Everyone, please look forward to it! We're so excited!
楽しみでござるな。そして、そして、最後。これがね、すごい、もう目玉。
I'm looking forward to it. And, and, finally. This is the big highlight.
ユニットオリジナル楽曲を、本日、初披露いたします！
We will perform our unit original song for the first time today!
わあー！これめっちゃいいから、マジで！
Wow! This is really good, seriously!
本当にいいから！めっちゃ聴いて。盛り上がるよね！
It's really good! Listen to it a lot. It's so exciting!
ありえないくらいいいでござるよね！
It's unbelievably good!
もうね、始まる前にスタッフさんが口ずさむくらい耳に残る！
It's so catchy that even the staff members were humming it before we started!
そうそう！しかもかっこいいんだよね！
Exactly! And it's so cool!
頑張ったよ！頑張ったよ、見てほしい。
We worked hard! We worked hard, so please watch it.
はい、ということで、本当に目白押しなんですけれども、
Yes, so it's truly packed with highlights,
早速ね、新メンバーの方を待たせておりますので、移動しましょう。
but we're already keeping the new member waiting, so let's move.
いらないって言われた新メンバー！手のかからない子だったら欲しいのよ。
The new member who was told they weren't needed! I want them if they don't need care.
ということで、新メンバーのところに、レッツ・ゴー！
So, to the new member's place, let's go!
レッツ・ゴー！
Let's go!
そこに跪け！
Kneel before us!
掃いて捨てるような現実を、
A reality like something swept away and discarded,
一刀両断、
We'll cut it down,
叩き斬る！
with a single stroke!
終わりなき輪廻なれば良し、これよ。
If it's an endless cycle of rebirth, then so be it.
漆黒の翼で誘おう。
Let us invite you with pitch-black wings.
我ら、平穏を蹂躙せしもの、秘密結社holoX！
We are the ones who trample over peace, Secret Society holoX!
今の決まったんじゃない！？
Didn't we nail that just now!?
めっちゃかっこいい！
It was so cool!
もう一回、次やってみる？
Should we try the next one?
あ、沙花叉、タカネになろう。
Ah, Sakamata, I'll be Takane.
あ、いろはになろう。
Ah, I'll be Iroha.
ござる、タカネ、ござる...何だかちょっと違う気がする。
Gozaru, Takane, gozaru... I feel like something's a bit off.
見たいぞ。いくぞ、せーの！
I want to see that. Let's go, ready, set!
せーの！そこに跪け！
Ready, set! Kneel before us!
そこに跪け！掃いて捨てるような現実を、
Kneel before us! A reality like something swept away and discarded,
一刀両断、叩き斬る！
We'll cut it down with a single stroke!
終わりなき輪廻...
Endless cycle of rebirth...
Now Loading
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし古（いにしえ）の...
Ancient one wandering in endless reincarnation...
漆黒の翼で誘（いざな）わん。
I shall beckon you with jet-black wings.
気持ち悪っ。
Gross.
我ら、エデンの星を統べるもの！
We are the rulers of the Planet Eden!
秘密結社...
Secret Society...
holoX！
holoX!
ござるござるござるござるござる...
Gozaru, gozaru, gozaru, gozaru...
違う！ バイズじゃねーよ！
No! I'm not "Buiz"!
忍者、忍者！
Ninja, ninja!
うるせー、そこで喧嘩すんな！
Shut up, don't fight there!
ひどいよ、これ。
This is terrible.
お前、ずっと言ってたいいんだろ。
You've been saying that the whole time.
ござるござるござるござる...
Gozaru, gozaru, gozaru...
うるせー、あいつら。
They're so loud.
喧嘩してるぞ、あいつら。
Look at them fighting.
喧嘩すんな、そこで。
Stop fighting over there.
仲良くして、本当に。ひどいな...
Get along, seriously. How awful...
変わってみる？
Want to switch?
似てるんだよな、これ。
This actually looks like you.
あ、今日こんこんやるんだよ。
Ah, I'm doing "Konkon" today.
え、誰になればいいんだ？
Wait, who should I be?
え、じゃあ風真いろはよ。
Then be Kazama Iroha.
あず、あず、じゃあチョキチョキしてほしいでござる。
Azu, azu, then I want you to do the "snip-snip," de gozaru.
はいはい。
Okay, okay.
しょうがないな。
Can't be helped.
よいしょ... よいしょ...
Heave-ho... heave-ho...
え、どうやるんだ？ こ、こうか？
Wait, how do you do it? L-Like this?
こっちか？
This way?
あ、どうだ？ こう...
Ah, how's this? Like...
こう... こうじゃない？ たぶん。
Like this... isn't it? Probably.
こう、こう。
Like this, like this.
はい。
Yes.
はい、みんな、そこに膝まずけー！
Now everyone, kneel before me!
そこに膝まずけー！
Kneel before me!
掃いて捨てるような喧騒は...
This worthless clamor...
一刀両断、叩き切る！
I shall slice it down with a single stroke!
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし古の...
Ancient one wandering in endless reincarnation...
漆黒の翼で誘わん！
I shall beckon you with jet-black wings.
我ら、エデンの星を統べるもの！
We are the rulers of the Planet Eden!
秘密結社 holoX！
Secret Society holoX!
ホロクサーねー！ ホロクサーねー！
HoloXer-nee! HoloXer-nee!
まっとかねー！ まっとかねー！
Mattokane! Mattokane!
ホロクサーねー、ホロクサーねー！
HoloXer-nee, HoloXer-nee!
ちょっと、忍者！
Hey, ninja!
忍者、忍者！
Ninja, ninja!
まっとかねー！
Mattokane!
ばか、忍者！
Stupid ninja!
まっとかねー！ まっとかねー！
Mattokane! Mattokane!
ということで、到着しましたー！
And with that, we have arrived!
わー！
Yay!
見て、このステージ！
Look at this stage!
どうだ！
How do you like it!
なんかバカでかいのがある！
There's something huge!
なんだこれ！？
What is this!?
何これ？
What is it?
実は、こちらはー！
Actually, this is...
holoXの予算を注ぎ込んで作りました...
Built by pouring in holoX's entire budget...
巨大クレーンゲームセットです！
...it's a giant crane game set!
え！？
What!?
予算なかったのって...
So the reason we had no budget...
お前か！？ お前か！？
...was you!? Was it you!?
え、え、え、何やってんの、こより！
Wait, what are you doing, Koyori!
給料払えなかったのお前のせいじゃねーか！
It's your fault we couldn't get our salaries paid!
えっ、だって、今日は1周年でさ...
Well, today is our 1st anniversary...
みんなでやるにはこういうの必要っしょ！
...so we need something like this for everyone to do together!
あ、経費で落とせってこと？
Oh, so you mean charge it as an expense?
あ、経費使った。
Ah, she used the expense account.
なるほど。
I see.
勝手に経費使うなよ！
Don't just use expenses on your own!
経費！ 経費！ 経費！
Expenses! Expenses! Expenses!
もう、なんだ、そうだったのか。
Jeez, so that's what happened.
だめだね、本当に。
That's really not good.
増やせないよ。
We can't increase the budget.
見て、中に入ってるの、もしかして...
Look, what's inside, could it be...
お！
Oh!
新メンバー！？
New members!?
そうなんです！ 新メンバーをいっぱい詰め込んでおきました！
That's right! I've packed it full of new members!
詰め込んだ！？
Packed them in!?
そう、新メンバーはですね...
Yes, the new members are...
皆さんなんです！ holoXerのみんな！
...all of you! Every holoXer out there!
やったー！
Yay!
新メンバー！ 新メンバー！
New members! New members!
なんか入ってきちゃったね。
They just kind of came in.
応援する立場から仲間になるってことだね。
So they're going from supporters to comrades.
新メンバー！ 新メンバー！
New members! New members!
そうなんですよ。ということで...
Exactly. And so...
今回の配信は私たちに仕えるholoXerのみんなを...
...in this stream, all the holoXers who serve us...
大量ゲットするというゲームをやっていきたいと思います！
...we're going to play a game to get a massive amount of them!
いぇーい！
Yay!
どうやって？ どうやって？
How? How?
いや、これ見たらわかるでしょ。
Well, you can tell just by looking at this.
どうやって？
How?
人間クレーンゲームで掴んで落として持ってくるんだ！
You use the Human Crane Game to grab them and bring them back!
わかった！ なるほど。
Got it! I see.
フィジカルで行くんだね。
So we're going physical.
掴むってこと？
You mean grab them?
でね、目標が一応ありましてー。
And, we have a goal.
手始めにね、友達100人作りたいということで...
To start, since we want to make 100 friends...
100体を集めていきたいと！
...we want to collect 100 of them!
安直！
How simplistic!
100人。多すぎじゃないかな...
100 people. Isn't that a bit much...?
でも100人も捕れたらすごいよね。
But it would be amazing if we could catch 100.
捕りたいなあ。
I want to catch them.
え、どうやって捕るの？
Wait, how do we catch them?
ギュッと握り締め、愛を込めて...
Hold them tight, with love...
ギュッと握り締めて持ってきて！
...hold them tight and bring them back!
わかった。
Got it.
なるほどね。
I see.
やってほしい！
I want you to do it!
というわけで、まずはクレーンゲームに入っている...
So first, to get the holoXers...
holoXerさんを手に入れるということで、最初のコーナーは！
...who are in the crane game, the first corner is!
せーの！
One, two!
大量ゲット!? holoXクレーン！
Massive GET!? holoX Crane!
大量GET!? holoXクレーン
Massive GET!? holoX Crane
はい。
Yes.
じゃあ早速ですけれども。
Well, without further ado.
クレーンになる人。
The person who will be the crane.
クレーン！？
The crane!?
ギュッてね、する人ね。
The one who does the "grabbing."
あと自転車を漕ぐ人？
And... a person to pedal the bicycle?
自転車を漕ぐ人？
A person to pedal the bicycle?
意味のわからない説明を読まされている。
I'm being made to read an explanation that makes no sense.
操作する人と操作補助で画面の切り替えとかをしたりする方。
The operator and the assistant who handles things like screen switching.
その4人でね、私たちをちょっと振り分けてやっていきたいと思います。
I want to divide the four of us into those roles.
頑張ってください。
Please do your best.
自転車って何だ？
What's the bicycle for?
実はー。
Actually...
うちは金がないじゃないですか。
...we don't have any money, right?
だから...
So...
…のギュンに必要な電力が足りなくって…
...the power needed for the final 'Gyun' is not enough...
何やってる…
What are you doing...
それを自給自足する！
So we'll produce it ourselves!
自家発電！
Self-power generation!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
えっ、あ、それが…
Eh, ah, and that is...
それが、これ！
That is, this!
これ？
This?
自転車？
A bicycle?
そう、自転車！
Yes, a bicycle!
繋いでくれば済む話だろうがよ！
You could just connect it to a socket!
えー、最後のギュンはやっぱりね、必要なんで！
Well, that final 'Gyun' is necessary after all!
自家発電しようってことでござるか？
So we're going to generate power ourselves?
そういうことでござる！
That's right!
頭脳派のやり方よ！
It's the brainy way!
おかしいだろ！ひらがなの「ずのう」だな、やっぱり。
That's weird! It's 'brain' spelled in hiragana after all.
ひらがなだ。
It's hiragana.
頭脳を働かせて作ったのが、これ！
This is what I made by using my brain!
それが頭脳か。
So this is the 'brain'.
じゃあね、とりあえず振り分けてみましょうか。
Well then, let's assign roles for now.
ということで、チャンスは2回あって…
So, there are two chances...
1回1ゲーム、3分になっております。制限時間は。
Each game is 3 minutes long. That's the time limit.
100人か…
100 people...
ということで、最初、体力が必要だから、自転車は。
So, first, since stamina is needed for the bicycle...
あー、もうそんな気がしてました。
Ah, I had a feeling about that.
さすが！
As expected!
任せてください。
Leave it to me.
任せてくださいよ！
Just leave it to me!
似合うね。
It suits you.
自転車か… なるほどでござる。
A bicycle... I see.
結構辛そうだな…
It looks pretty tough...
でも体力強いし。
But you have strong stamina.
大丈夫、大丈夫、いけるいける！
It's okay, it's okay, I can do it!
大丈夫。
It's okay.
頑張れ！
Do your best!
頑張れじゃないんだよ！
It's not 'do your best'!
働かなきゃダメなんでござるか？
I have to work too?
あ、じゃあ、吊るされるか。
Ah, then, will you be suspended?
クレーン、クレーンになる人。お前だ！
The one who becomes the crane. It's you!
えー！？私！？
Eh!? Me!?
イェーイ！
Yeah!
私！？
Me!?
うわああああ！
Waaaaah!
胸で挟んでいこう！
Catch them with your chest!
胸で挟む！？
With my chest!?
ということで、こよりは操作をしてもらって。
So, Koyori, you operate the crane.
こよりの補佐をね、私がさせていただきます。
And I will assist you.
画面切り替えよろしくな！
Screen switching, please!
よろしく、頼むぞ！頑張ろうな！
I'm counting on you! Let's do our best!
頑張ろうなー！
Let's do our best!
これはね、掴む方の腕とね…
This is about the skill of the grabber...
電力をちゃんと保てられるかがね…
And whether the power can be properly maintained...
ただこうやって操作するだけじゃなくて。
It's not just about operating it.
そうそうそう。
Right, right, right.
二人の腕にかかってますね！
It depends on the skill of you two!
ということで、二人ともどうだ？準備はできてるのかな？
So, how are you two? Are you ready?
凄い…
Amazing...
あ、吊るされてるんですけど。
Ah, I'm being suspended.
おー、似合ってる似合ってる！
Oh, it suits you, it suits you!
イェーイ！
Yeah!
家にありそう。
Looks like it belongs in your house.
はい、クロヱは？
Okay, how about Chloe?
助けてください！
Please help me!
いいね！いい逃げ方！
Nice! Nice way to escape!
海の中みたいじゃん。
Looks like you're in the sea.
クロエの泳ぎ！
Chloe's swimming!
いいじゃん。
Nice.
誰か助けて！
Someone help me!
お船に入れない！
I can't get into the ship!
似合ってるよ！
It suits you!
何とかなる、何とかなる！
It'll be fine, it'll be fine!
ぶらぶらする…
I'm dangling...
ということでね、最初のチャレンジ、早速行きましょう。
So, let's start the first challenge right away.
準備はいいか、いろはとクロヱ！
Are you ready, Iroha and Chloe!
大丈夫でござる！
I'm ready!
オッケー！
Okay!
ということで、制限時間は3分。
So, the time limit is 3 minutes.
3分で何個取れるか、やっていきましょう！
Let's see how many we can get in 3 minutes!
オッケー！頑張ろう！
Okay! Let's do our best!
最初のチャレンジ、スタート！
First challenge, start!
じゃあ、あの黄色いのが見えてるからさ！
Well, I can see the yellow ones!
黄色いのだ！
The yellow ones!
黄色いのだよ、金色！
The yellow ones, gold!
金色、金色！
Gold, gold!
金の玉！？
Golden balls!?
金の玉、金の玉！
Golden balls, golden balls!
行くよ、はい、金の玉！
Going, okay, golden balls!
漕いで漕いで漕いで！
Pedal, pedal, pedal!
金の玉、金の玉！
Golden balls, golden balls!
行くよ！はい！
Going! Okay!
漕いで、漕いで！
Pedal, pedal!
取れない！
I can't get it!
エイム悪いわ！
Your aim is bad!
エイムは腕の問題だろ！
Aim is a matter of the arms!
自分で行くよ！
I'll go myself!
はいよ！
Okay!
漕いで、まだ漕いで！
Pedal, keep pedaling!
漕いで、もっと漕いで！
Pedal, pedal more!
まだ、まだ！
More, more!
はい！離して！
Okay! Release!
はい、離します！
Okay, releasing!
あー！
Ah!
あれ？胸に挟まってなかった。
Huh? It wasn't caught in my chest.
挟まらなかったかな。
It didn't get caught.
あと2分ちょっとあるよ。
There's still a bit over 2 minutes left.
2分も吊るされるんですか！？
I'm going to be suspended for 2 minutes!?
金色いけんじゃない？
Can't we get the gold one?
行けそう、行けそう！
Looks like we can, looks like we can!
痛い痛い痛い！そこじゃない！
Ow ow ow! Not there!
行け行け行け！
Go go go!
いい加減にしろ！違う違う！
Give me a break! No, no!
行け行け行け！
Go go go!
頑張れ、頑張れ！
Go for it, go for it!
はいはいはい！
Yes yes yes!
漕いで、漕いで、もっと漕いで！
Pedal, pedal, pedal more!
あとちょっと！
Just a bit more!
止まります、はい！
Stopping, okay!
漕いで、漕いで、漕いで！
Pedal, pedal, pedal!
はい！
Yes!
離して、はい！
Release, okay!
あれ？
Huh?
あ！ナイス！
Ah! Nice!
あまりに早い重力で落ちていった。
It fell with such fast gravity.
重力に影響されちゃって。
Influenced by gravity.
さっきの金色のやつ取ってくれよ！
Take that golden one from before!
どこにあんだ、どこにあんだ？
Where is it, where is it?
あと1分半あるから！
There's still a minute and a half left!
もっともっともっと！
More more more!
エイムは腕でどうにかして！
Do something about the aim with your arms!
行くよ、漕いで漕いで！
Going, pedal pedal!
行け行け行け！
Go go go!
取れた！取れた！
Got it! Got it!
金の取れた！
Got the gold one!
重い重い重い！
It's heavy heavy heavy!
ナイス、ナイス！
Nice, nice!
バタバタしてる…
It's acting up...
暴れるんだけど！
It's acting up!
オッケーオッケー、取れた？
Okay okay, did you get it?
取れた、取れた！
Got it, got it!
はい、離して、はい！
Okay, release, okay!
あー！ナイス！素晴らしい！
Ah! Nice! Wonderful!
行くぞ、行くぞ！
Let's go, let's go!
あと10秒！
10 seconds left!
行け、行け！
Go, go!
黒、黒！
Black, black!
行け行け行け！
Go go go!
行けー！
Go-!
終了！
Finish!
はい！行って行って！
Yes! Go, go!
行け行け！いいぞいいぞ！
Go, go! Looking good!
頑張れ沙花叉！行け行け！
Go for it, Sakamata! Go, go!
あ、なんか上の方に…行け行け！
Ah, it's going up... Go, go!
あと少し！
Just a bit more!
あと20秒！あと20秒！
20 seconds left! 20 seconds left!
行ける行ける！頑張れ頑張れ！
You can do it! Keep going!
え、待って！赤くない？赤くない？
Wait, isn't it red? Isn't it red?
離せ離せ！離して！
Release it! Let go!
行ける行ける！はい、はい！
You can do it! Yes, yes!
店員さん！店員さん呼んで！店員さん！
Clerk! Call the clerk! Clerk!
はい、ということで何体だった？
So, how many was it?
はい、ということで黄色も取って14体！大収穫です！
Alright, so with the gold one, that's 14! A great harvest!
14体？…え、あと一回しかできないのに14？
14?! ...Eh, even though there's only one try left, 14?
黄色ね、取ってくれなかったからな…
Because you didn't get the gold one...
凄く黄色のそばに落ちたのにね！
It fell right next to the gold one!
お前ら！助けてよ！
You guys! Help me!
ルイ姉は何も悪くないよね。
Lui-nee isn't at fault at all, right?
下手クソなんだよ！
You're so bad at this!
待って、なんか…どれだけ大変だと思ってんだよ、こっち！
Wait... how hard do you think it is for me?!
そんなことないでござるよ。重たいでござるよ。
That's not true. It was heavy.
なんで？重い？
Why? Is it heavy?
自転車漕いでいる人がわかるの？重い？
Does the person pedaling the bike feel it? Is it heavy?
でも待って、いろはが息がちょっと上がってるから。
But wait, Iroha is a bit out of breath.
本当に最後頑張ったら…
I really did my best at the end...
じゃあ、もう一回いろは行ける？
Then, can Iroha go again?
いや、バカバカ！何言ってんの？
No, you idiot! What are you saying?
お前がやるんだよ！
You're the one doing it!
なんかね、散々って言ってたから…
Since you were saying such harsh things...
上のものをやらせてやるよ。
I'll let you be the one on top.
お前がクレーンになって、お前が捕獲。
You become the crane, and you catch them.
仕方ないな。ルイにやらせてください。
Can't be helped. Please let Lui do it.
マジでさ、思ってる以上にやばいことスタートしたよね。
Seriously, we started something way crazier than I thought.
これマジでやばい。本当にやばいでござるよ。
This is seriously bad. It's really bad.
いろはちゃんが息上がってて、沙花叉も大変なことになってるからね。
Iroha-chan is out of breath, and Sakamata is in a bit of a state too.
症状も見せられないよが…
I can't even show the situation...
え、でも空飛べる気持ちになりそうだから大丈夫かな？
Eh, but I might feel like I'm flying in the sky, so will it be okay?
舐めてもらったら困るでござる。
Don't underestimate it.
俺たち飛んだしね。
We flew too, right?
そろそろ準備ができたんじゃないか？
Isn't it about time the preparations are finished?
現場の鷹嶺さん！鷹嶺さん！
Takane-san on the scene! Takane-san!
あ、いいでござるな。似合うんよ、なんか爽やか。
Ah, that's good. It suits you, looks refreshing.
奥様みたいだね。ジムに来た奥様。
Like a housewife. A housewife who came to the gym.
爽やかだな。口説きたいな。
How refreshing. I want to hit on her.
え、じゃあ、こよりちゃん？発進！
Eh, so, Koyori-chan? Launch!
こよりちゃん、飛んでおります！
Koyori-chan, she's flying!
白鳥になっている！こよりさん！
She's becoming a swan! Koyori-san!
お前、覚えてるよ、先までの。
You, I'll remember what happened until now.
丁寧に、丁寧に扱ってくださいね！
Handle me gently, handle me gently, please!
はい、というわけで丁寧に扱いますよ！
Yes, so I will handle you gently!
絶対扱わねえ、こいつ！
No way she'll handle you gently!
準備ができたみたいなんんで。ゲームスタート！
Looks like preparations are ready. Game start!
私は見てるだけでいいから。
I'm fine just watching.
エイム力ってもの見せてくださいよ！
Please show me your aiming skills!
黄色、黄色が…赤さが気になるんだけど。
Gold, the gold... but I'm worried about the red.
行ける行ける！行け行け行け！
You can do it! Go, go, go!
行け行け！
Go, go!
おっけー！また胸熱を感じる。
Okay! I'm feeling that hot-bloodedness again.
上の方に存在よ。良さそう！
It's up there. Looking good!
ちょっとあとちょっとが取れないんだな。
Ah, I just can't get that last bit.
行ける行ける！行け行け行け！
You can do it! Go, go, go!
ことこと…なんだこれ？
Kotto kotto... what's this?
え、赤？離せ離せ離せ！
Eh, red? Release it! Let go!
ないないない、赤って！
No no no, red?!
赤は爆発だね。
Red means explosion.
こよりちゃん、無事ですか？大丈夫ですか？
Koyori-chan, are you safe? Are you okay?
現場のこよりさん、大丈夫ですか？
Koyori-san on the scene, are you okay?
こより混ぜてない…聞いてないよ！
Koyori, don't mix... I didn't hear about this!
爆発したら3分より前で終わってしまう。
If it explodes, it ends before the 3 minutes are up.
エイム下手クソ！もう一回もう一回！
Your aiming is so bad! One more time, one more time!
叩け叩け！こよりを叩け！
Hit it, hit it! Hit Koyori!
まだやってもいいらしいです。
Looks like we can still keep going.
まだやっていいの？いいの？やるやる！
We can still do it? Really? Let's do it!
頑張れ！黄色の玉まで持ってって！
Good luck! Take it to the gold ball!
行け行け行け！
Go, go, go!
いいんじゃない！いいんじゃない！
Looking good! Looking good!
行け！行け！行け！
Go! Go! Go!
金！金！金！
Gold! Gold! Gold!
行け行け行け！
Go, go, go!
あー！危ない危ない！
Ah! Careful, careful!
行け行け行け！
Go, go, go!
こんこより！
Kon-Koyori!
はい！
Yes!
ノーマル、ノーマルホロックス！
Normal, normal holoX!
オッケーオッケーオッケー！
Okay, okay, okay!
ちゅっちゅっちゅっ！
Chu, chu, chu!
待って、ちょっと辛い！
Wait, this is tough!
早く、早く、早く！
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
早く！早く！
Hurry! Hurry!
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
あ、オッケー！
Ah, okay!
ナイスナイスナイス！金色欲しいな、金色。
Nice, nice, nice! I want the gold one.
金色取りたいよ。
I want to get a gold one.
金色どこだ？あ、この辺？
Where's the gold one? Ah, around here?
この辺にするか。
Let's go for this spot.
あ、いいんじゃない？
Ah, looking good!
オッケー、うん。行け行け行け！
Okay, yeah. Go, go, go!
行け行け、金色取れー！
Go, go, get the gold one!
きえーん！
Kie-n!
どーしよー！なんでだよー！
What should I do?! Why did that happen?!
こんこより、こんこより、こんこよりー！
Kon-Koyori, Kon-Koyori, Kon-Koyori!
おかしい！
This is strange!
なんでだよー、さっきのままで良かった。
Why?! It was fine just a moment ago.
そのまま、そのまま。
Keep going, keep going.
頑張ってんだー！
I'm trying my best!
いいんじゃない？
Looking good?
はい、はい！
Yes, yes!
はい！はい！オッケー、オッケー！
Yes! Yes! Okay, okay!
え、ちょっと、金、金、金、金！
Wait, gold, gold, gold, gold!
金色あそこだ！あ、取れた取れた！
The gold one is there! Ah, I got it!
行け行け、行け行け！
Go, go, go, go!
あー頑張れ頑張れ！左、左、もうちょい左。
Ah, keep going! Left, left, a bit more left.
はい、はい！
Yes, yes!
行けー！金色取れー！
Go! Get the gold one!
やったー！金色取れた！
Yay! I got a gold one!
頑張れ、頑張れ！
Keep going, keep going!
なんでこんなに運が悪いんだよ。
Why is my luck so bad?
終わりです！
That's the end!
やばーい！
No way!
落として、落として！
Drop it, drop it!
落として！落として！
Drop it! Drop it!
落として！
Drop it!
おっちー！
Falling!
なんてこったー！時間切れ！
Oh my god! Time's up!
え、でもこれってあれでしょ。ゲームセンター的に行くとさ。
Wait, but isn't this like an arcade?
100個入れたらこのまま開いて落ちるんじゃない？
If you put in 100, won't it just open and drop?
確かに、確かに。
True, true.
こんこよりのことが好きすぎて、もうおっぱいから離れなかった。
I loved the toys too much, I couldn't let go of them.
なんてだよ、しょうがないわ。
Why? It can't be helped.
頑張ったのになー。離れなかった。
I tried so hard... but I couldn't let go.
やっぱアームが悪いな。
The arm must be the problem.
これ作ったのこんこよりだからね。
Koyori's the one who made this, though.
作ったこんこよりが悪いな。
Then it's Koyori's fault for making it.
ヒィー！みんな楽しかったでしょ！
Hee! Everyone had fun, right?!
大丈夫？大丈夫？
Are you okay? Are you okay?
大丈夫、大丈夫。
I'm okay, I'm okay.
いろは、ごめん。いろは、ごめん。すごい辛かった。
Iroha, sorry. Iroha, sorry. It was really tough.
大丈夫！よー頑張ったね。大丈夫だよ。
It's okay! You did a great job. It's fine.
大丈夫、大丈夫。
It's okay, it's okay.
ごめんね。
Sorry.
いやーでもなかなか難しかったね。やっぱ作るものは。
Wow, but that was quite difficult. Creating things is hard.
いや、でもがっつり遊べて楽しかったと思うんだよね。
Well, but I think it was fun to just play around.
まあ楽しかったけどね。ただもう目標の100体には。
Well, it was fun. But as for the goal of 100...
届いておりません！
We didn't reach it!
全然届いてない！合計17体！
Not even close! 17 in total!
あっらー！
Oh boy!
ということでね、はい。全然目標に達していないので。
So, yes. Since we haven't reached our goal at all...
次のゲーム、用意しているみたいなので。
It seems they have the next game ready.
そこでちょっと挽回をしていきましょう！
Let's try to make up for it there!
やったー！
Yay!
はい、ということで。次のゲーム会場、用意お願いします！
Alright then. Please set up the next game venue!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
ということで、準備をしてもらっていますよ。
And so, they are getting things ready.
どっち？どこだ？
Which way? Where is it?
迷子になるでござる。
I'm going to get lost.
こっちだ、こっちだ。迷子になるでござる。ひどい。
This way, this way. I'm getting lost. Terrible.
随分、なんか広い部屋に行くんですな。
We're going to quite a large room, aren't we?
あれか？ということでちょっと、私は準備ができたから。
Is it that? Well, since I'm ready...
コメント見るか。ね、コメント見るか。
I'll look at the comments. Yeah, let's look at the comments.
ぱちぱち、ゴーゴー！見えてるよ、見えてるよ！
Applause, go go! I see you, I see you!
どうだったクレーンゲーム？
How was the crane game?
なあ、頑張ったでしょ。
See, we tried hard.
頑張ったよ。エイムとかの問題っていうかさ。
We did. It's not really a matter of aim...
結構もう分からなかった、運だったね。
I didn't really understand it, it was just luck.
難しかったねー。それだけホロックスの皆が取ってくれるってことだよね。
It was hard. It just shows how much everyone wants holoX.
いっぱいいたからね、なかなか金色を狙えなかったよね。
There were so many, it was hard to target the gold ones.
やほー、見てるー？
Yoo-hoo, are you watching?
見てる、見てるよ。面白かったって言ってくれてる。
Watching, watching. They're saying it was funny.
よかったー。
I'm glad.
あんまり金色がね、ゲットできなかったから本当に。
We couldn't really get many gold ones, honestly.
1個しか！
Only one!
1個しか取れてなかった。っていうかさ、赤がさ。
We only got one. And by the way, the red ones...
爆発するってうちら知らなかった。
We didn't know they would explode.
ねえ、あれは事前に言ってくれよ！
Hey, tell us that in advance!
勝手に混ぜたよ。そう、こよは混ぜてないよ。
They mixed them in. Yeah, Koyo didn't mix them.
言ってくれよ！爆発物ダメでござるよ！
Tell us! Explosives are a no-go!
爆発落ちなんて最低。最低！
An explosive ending is the worst. The worst!
やめてよ、爆発落ちは刺さる、こんこよ。
Stop it, explosive endings hit too hard, Koyori.
爆発落ちって言えばオープニングも爆発落ちだったね。
Speaking of explosive endings, the opening was one too.
面白かったわ。はい、はい、はい。
That was funny. Yes, yes, yes.
ドーン！面白かった。
Boom! That was funny.
だいぶなんか、笑顔で最後爆破する感じ。
It was kind of a feeling of exploding with a smile.
危なかったでござるよね。
That was dangerous, wasn't it?
かっこよく投げられたら良かったんだけどね。
It would have been better if we could have thrown coolly.
いや、もっとかっこよくリベンジしたいよね、5人で。
No, I want to get revenge even more coolly with us five.
ラプラス上手そうだしね。
La+ seems like she'd be good at it.
せっかく予算使ったしね。もったいない。
We used the budget for it, after all. It's a waste.
そうだ。これっきり、1回っきりのために使ったんだ。
Right. We used it just for this one time.
ふざけんなよ、我々の給料が。
Don't screw with me, our salaries went into this.
でもあれを置いとく倉庫も高そうだね。
But a warehouse to store that would probably be expensive.
確かに。分解しよう、分解。
True. Let's dismantle it, dismantle.
リサイクル、リサイクル。嘘だろ。
Recycle, recycle. You're kidding.
誰か買い取ってくれる人がいたらね。
If there's someone who'll buy it.
値段出します、1万円から。
I'll set a price, starting from 10,000 yen.
1万円。
10,000 yen.
目の前にもうやばそうなものが。
There's already something crazy-looking in front of us.
さてさて、これ何ですか？
Now then, what is this?
なんか見たことあるよな...
I feel like I've seen this before...
これ大丈夫？
Is this okay?
あの、皆様しれっとね、我々ちょっと
Um, everyone, we've been quietly brought
ヤバいものの目の前に連れてこられてるんだよね。
in front of something quite dangerous.
ヤバいってより楽しそうだけど！
It looks more fun than dangerous!
楽しそうでござるね！
It looks fun!
え〜でもなんかヤバイ... デカくない？
Eh, but it looks dangerous... isn't it huge?
夢のような... こういうのやってみたいと思ってたんですよ。
It's like a dream... I've thought about wanting to try something like this.
助かるー！
Glad to hear!
嬉しい！
I'm happy!
皆何だと思う？予想して予想。
What do you all think it is? Guess, guess.
皆殿の反応も気にかかるでござる。
I'm curious about the audience's reaction too.
何が起こってんだ？
What's happening?
ギロチンって言われてる！
Someone said 'guillotine'!
何でやりたいんだよ！おかしいだろ！
Why would you want to do that! That's crazy!
ギロチンでどうやってホロクスさ増やすんや！
How do you increase Holoxsa with a guillotine?!
やだでござるね！
I don't like that!
切って、切って、増やす...
Cut them, cut them, and increase...
1を2にして...
Turn one into two...
スライムじゃないんだから、ホロクスさは！
Holoxsa aren't slimes!
肝出しバンジー...
Liver-spilling bungee...
「SASUKE」って言われてる。
They're saying "SASUKE".
あ〜「SASUKE」ね。やってみたいよね。
Ah, "SASUKE". You'd want to try that.
いややってみたいか？いや無理だが。
Wait, do you really want to? No, it's impossible.
跳べるけど...
You can jump, but...
これ泣きそうだどな。
I feel like I'd cry.
「そんな〜」って泣いて...
Crying like "No way~"...
アスレチック。
Athletics.
ね、コメント欄がめちゃスロット民なんだけど。
Hey, the comment section is full of slot fans.
いや、やりてえな！やってたな。
No, I want to do it! We used to do it.
やりたいでござる！
I want to do it!
もっと長々とやりてえよ。1時間やりてえ。
I want to do it for a long, long time. I want to do it for an hour.
モグラ叩き！いいね！
Whack-a-mole! That's good!
皆がモグラになって...
Everyone becomes a mole...
誰かが叩く？
Does someone hit them?
それぞれに殴られる。それぞれが殴る。
Everyone gets hit. Everyone hits.
日頃の「おらぁ！」っていうのを込めて。
Putting in our daily "Rah!" feelings.
何か恨みが溜まってんのか？大丈夫？
Are you harboring some grudges? Are you okay?
ご褒美じゃん、ご褒美！
It's a reward, a reward!
いいね！
Nice!
そろそろか？そろそろ来るか？
Is it about time? Is it coming soon?
行けるかな？行けるのかな？
Can we go? I wonder if we can.
来たー！
It's here!
見えたか？見えたかこっち！
Did you see it? Did you see it, this way!
見えたー！
We saw it!
見えたかね？見えたかね？
Did you see it? Did you see it?
せーの！
Ready, set...
操れ！巨大シーソー！
Operate! Giant Seesaw!
シーソーシーソー。ということで、これは何だ？
Seesaw, seesaw. So, what is this?
あれ、見たことあるね！
Hey, I've seen that before!
見たことある！これ... 大丈夫なんですかね？
I've seen it! Is this... okay?
大丈夫です！わかんないけど、多分大丈夫でござる。
It's fine! I don't know, but it's probably fine.
記憶をたどると、上からボールが落ちてくる！
If I recall my memories, balls fall from the top!
皆見て、揺れてるぞ！ヤバいぞ！
Everyone look, it's shaking! This is bad!
ということで、次は先ほどゲットしたホロクスさを賭けて、このシーソーをね、移動して...
So, next, we'll bet the Holoxsa we just got, and move this seesaw...
...このように。見えたかな？移動すると...
...like this. See? If we move...
おー、すごいすごい！傾く！
Oh, wow! It tilts!
片方でこっちに移動すると... おー、傾くすごい！
If one side moves this way... oh, it tilts, wow!
傾きますので、このようにね移動をして、最後にゴールにホロクスさを入れて！
Since it tilts, we move like this, and finally put the Holoxsa into the goal!
おーすごい、動いてるねゴール！
Oh, wow, the goal is moving!
動くゴールになっておりますのでね。4人で力を合わせて...
It's a moving goal. So the four of us need to work together...
ホロクスさが出航する！
The Holoxsa are setting sail!
ゴールをしたら、1体ゲット！
If we goal, we get one!
えっ！ってことは、20倍にできるってこと？
Eh! Does that mean we can make it 20 times more?
そうそう、1体で20個！
Right, right. 20 for each one!
え、すごいじゃん！えっ、あとじゃあ5個取ったらもう勝ち？
Wow, that's amazing! So, if we get 5 more, we win?
そう、勝ち！そうだね、簡単じゃんね！
Yes, we win! Right, it's easy!
制限時間はね、1ゲーム3分になっております。
The time limit is 3 minutes per game.
なので100体ね、こちらで目指して頑張っていきましょう！
So let's aim for 100 here and do our best!
イエーイ！頑張れー！
Yay! Let's go!
ということで、もう準備はいいですか？早速やっていきますけれども。
So, are you ready? We'll start right away.
1ゲーム目行きましょう！皆もね応援しててね！
Let's go for the first game! Everyone, please cheer for us!
コロコロ転がってる気分になってね！
Feel like you're rolling around too!
ということで、1ゲーム目スタート！
So, game one, start!
スタート！落ちてくる？落ちてくる！
Start! Is it falling? It's falling!
こっちこっち！行け行け行け！次次頑張れ！
This way, this way! Go go go! Next, next, do your best!
速い！速い！ちょっと難しい、ちょっと早めになってきた。
Fast! Fast! It's a bit difficult, it got a bit faster.
まあまあまだまだ！大丈夫！
Well, well, not yet! It's okay!
オッケー！行け行け、こっちこっち！結構勢いが付くから！
Okay! Go go, this way, this way! It gains quite a bit of momentum!
速い速い速い速い！こっちこっち！速い！速い！
Fast fast fast fast! This way, this way! Fast! Fast!
速い！速い！こっちこっち！速い！速い！
Fast! Fast! This way, this way! Fast! Fast!
速い！転がる！転がる！おいで、おいで！オッケーオッケー！
Fast! It's rolling! It's rolling! Come on, come on! Okay, okay!
速い！オッケーオッケー！もっともっともっとこっち、もっとこっち！
Fast! Okay, okay! More, more, more this way, more this way!
あ、もっとこっち！逃げなくていいんだよ、大丈夫だよ！
Ah, more this way! You don't have to run away, it's okay!
大丈夫だよ！ホロクスさがいるよ！はいはいはい！オッケーオッケー！
It's okay! Holoxsa is here! Yes yes yes! Okay, okay!
せーの！ボート、ボート、ボート！と考えたら... でもこっちちょっと...
Ready, set! Boat, boat, boat! Thinking about it... but this way a bit...
行け行け行け！いっぱい頑張れ！
Go go go! Do your best with lots of them!
やだー！行け行け！
No way! Go go!
すごいすごいすごい！やったやったやった！
Amazing, amazing! We did it, we did it!
あ、そんなことしてる場合じゃなくない？
Ah, isn't this no time for that?
あ、まだまだ来てる！そうだ、3分だから！
Ah, more are coming! That's right, it's 3 minutes!
ちゃんとね！はいはいはい！次次！ここが速くて！
Properly! Yes yes yes! Next, next! This part is fast!
うわあああああ！
Waaaaaah!
行け、行け！
Go, go!
むず！
This is hard!
いや、むず、あそこむず、難しすぎ！
No, it's hard. That part is hard. Too difficult!
慣性が...
The inertia is...
おいで、おいで、おいで、おいで！
Come here, come here, come here!
できた！いいよいいよ！
I did it! Good, good!
ここが速いから、早めに、すぐに早めに！
This part is fast, so do it early, quickly!
早めに早めに！オッケーオッケー！
Early, early! OK OK!
いやあああ！
Kyaaaa!
待て待て、まだまだまだ...
Wait, wait, not yet, not yet...
こっちこっち、おいで、おいで！
This way, this way. Come here!
行け行け、危ない危ない！
Go go! Careful, careful!
いやああああ！行け行け行け！
Kyaaaaa! Go go go!
待て、こっちこっちこっち！
Wait, this way, this way!
オッケーオッケー、ここ、ここ！
OK OK, here, here!
今だ！行け行け行け行け！
Now! Go go go go!
おいしい！おいしい！
Sweet! Nice!
待て待てちょっと待って、ちょっとここで調整して。
Wait wait, hold on. Adjust it here a bit.
行け行け行け行け！ナイス！
Go go go go! Nice!
いやああああ！
Kyaaaaa!
53個か！え、上手くね？
53 points! Hey, aren't we good at this?
上手くね？あ、喜んでる場合じゃない。
Aren't we? Oh, this is no time to be celebrating.
今だ！ゴミ、ゴミ人数になっちゃってる。
Now! We're becoming trash people.
いいよ、5人、5人。
It's fine, 5 people, 5 people.
始め！始め、始め！
Start! Start, start!
いやああああ！そっちって言ったじゃん！
Kyaaaaa! I told you that way!
あと50秒、あと50秒！
50 seconds left, 50 seconds left!
ゴミになっちゃってるよ。
We're turning into trash.
こっちこっち！行け行け行け行け！
This way, this way! Go go go go!
行け行け行け、危ない危ない！
Go go go, careful, careful!
こっちこっちこっち！
This way, this way!
あそこ危険だからね、黒いバー。
That part is dangerous, the black bar.
あ、行け行け行け行け！
Ah, go go go go!
頑張れ！ナイスナイス！
Good luck! Nice nice!
あ、省エネし始めた、省エネ。
Ah, they're starting to slack off.
え、あれ？なんか指示だけして動いてない。
Eh, huh? Someone is just giving orders and not moving.
おい、こっち来んな、おい。
Hey, don't come this way, hey.
待て待て待て、行け行け行け、危ない！
Wait wait wait, go go go, careful!
喧嘩してる場合じゃない！
This is no time for fighting!
調整、調整、調整...
Adjust, adjust, adjust...
え、やばくないこれ？行け行け行け！
Eh, isn't this bad? Go go go!
待て待て待て待て！やめてやめて！
Wait wait wait! Stop, stop!
まず一回ここで、傾いて...
First, tilt it here once...
え、なんかあいつズルズルいってるけど。
Eh, she's just sliding along.
一瞬早く！今、行け行け行け！
A bit faster! Now, go go go!
行け行け行け、行け行け！
Go go go, go go!
ああああああ！こっちこっちこっち！
Aaaaaaaah! This way, this way!
っていうか、結構つらいな。
I mean, this is pretty tough.
疲れた。
I'm exhausted.
すごい、30mシャトルランだね、これ。
It's like a 30m shuttle run.
ということで、今合計が51、半分まで来ましたね。
So our current total is 51. We've reached the halfway point.
ね。え、でもだいぶ。
Right. But that's a lot.
あと一回すればいいんじゃない？そろそろ慣れてきたし。
Maybe one more time? We're starting to get the hang of it.
ね。もう一回やらせていただけますか？
Yeah. Can we try one more time?
オッケー！やったー！やったー！
OK! Yay! Hooray!
ということで、もう一回やっていきましょう。
Alright, let's go for it again.
今度はね、でも慣れてきたから。
This time, since we're used to it...
大丈夫なんじゃないかな？
I think we'll be fine.
多分大丈夫でしょう。
It'll probably be fine.
みんな頑張ろう。っていうかこら、指示厨になってる。
Let's do our best. Hey, you're just a back-seat driver!
ずっとそこにいていいの？
Is it okay for you to stay there?
あれ？よし、じゃあ頑張ってもらおうかな。
Huh? Alright, I'll let you do your best then.
おい、指示厨になろうか！
Hey, I'll be the one giving orders!
これ、普通に三段目から行けね？
Can't we just go from the third level?
え、待って待って、こら！三段目から行くよ。
Wait, wait! Let's go from the third level.
こっち、こっちの三段目で。
This way, from this third level.
結構外に行くね。あれ？三段目から行く？
It goes outside quite a bit. Wait, from the third level?
あ、やろうやろう。指示やればいいのね、5人で。
Let's do it. We just need to follow orders, all five of us.
よしオッケー。ということで、二回目のゲーム、スタート！
Alright, OK. So, second game, start!
こっち傾けておいて、行け行け！
Keep it tilted this way. Go, go!
今じゃない？今じゃない？
Isn't it now? Isn't it now?
ここで三段目で待ってればいい。
We just need to wait here at the third level.
待って待て、行け行け行け行け！
Wait, wait! Go go go go!
いやああああ！あー、行け行け！
Waaaaaaah! Ah, go go!
え、でもいけそうだよ、行け行け行け！
Wait, we can do this! Go go go!
待て、このまま...ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って。
Wait, stay like this... hold on, hold on.
次、次こっち。置いてまず。
Next, next is this way. Place it first.
待て、早めに！早めに！行け行け行け！
Wait, early! Do it early! Go go go!
行け行け行け！いけそう、ここでいけそう！
Go go go! We can do it! We can do it here!
行け、あー！やっぱり5個はダメなのか。
Go, ah! I guess 5 is no good after all.
あ、待って！黄色って何だ？
Ah, wait! What's the yellow one?
黄色何？黄色何？
What's yellow? What's the yellow one?
まずくない？大丈夫？これちゃんとやったほうがいいんじゃない？
Isn't this bad? Is it OK? Shouldn't we do this properly?
ね、三段目から、そうだね。
Yeah, from the third level. That's right.
一個一個ちゃんとやろうぜ。黄色は何になる？
Let's do them one by one properly. What does yellow do?
黄色はなんて...何ですか？もうわかんない！
What does yellow... what is it? I don't know anymore!
ああ、黄色もう一個来た！
Ah, another yellow one came!
え、黄色99？黄色99？
Eh, yellow is 99? 99 for yellow?
99！99！マジで！
99! 99! Seriously!
おいしいぞ、これだけでマジで！
This is sweet! This alone is huge, seriously!
まだ行け、99！金の玉だ、もう。
Keep going, 99! It's a golden ball now!
金の玉、でっけー、99！宝玉だ！
It's a huge golden ball, 99! A treasure ball!
まだまだまだ！あーやばい！むず！
Not yet, not yet! Ah, crap! It's hard!
あと一個！あと一個！
One more! One more!
え、待ってマジで？あれ二個取ってたっけ私。
Wait, seriously? Did I get two of those?
あれはあの増やすやつ。金の玉がまだまだまだ...
That was the multiplier one. The golden ball isn't ready yet...
行け行け行け！オッケー！行こう！
Go go go! OK! Let's go!
頑張れ頑張れ！増やせ増やせ！
Good luck! Multiply them, multiply them!
すごい真剣になってる。
We're getting really serious.
皆さん聞こえないかもしれないけど、今まででマジで真剣。
You might not be able to hear us, but we've never been more serious.
入れなきゃという使命感！
We feel a sense of duty to get it in!
全力！こっち！落ちてここ！
Full power! This way! Fall here!
転がり方が独特...
The way it rolls is so unique...
息ができない。あ、もうちょっと、あとここで待って。
I can't breathe. Ah, just a bit more. Wait here.
いやああああ！オッケー！行け行け！
Waaaaaaah! OK! Go go!
やったー！行け行け！いやああああ！
We did it! Go go! Kyaaaaa!
これおかしい！ちょっとこの台座壊れてます！
This is weird! This platform is broken!
5名で！
With five people!
揺れ！巨大シーソー！
Swaying! Giant Seesaw!
1000!
あれ？思ったより行けたな。
Oh? We did better than I thought.
最初のなんだったんだ。
What was that at first?
しかもズルしようとしてて私達。
And we were even trying to cheat.
ねえ。全然あれ入れられなかったね。
Yeah. We couldn't get any in at all.
横着はダメ。
No cutting corners.
ということでね、目標の1000回よりもはるかに上で...
So, we're far above our goal of 1000...
もう疲れちゃった、ちょっと待って。
I'm already tired, wait a second.
9000回！
9000!
ゲットできたね。
We got it, didn't we?
ということで目標達成したので、アジトに戻りましょうか、みんなと一緒にね。
So, since we achieved our goal, shall we head back to the hideout together?
はい！
Yes!
ということで、アジトにレッツゴー！
So, let's go to the hideout!
ちょっとさ、今ここでさ、ラプラスいないからさ、ラプラスのさ、いい所言っていかない？
Hey, since La+ isn't here right now, why don't we talk about her good points?
あ、いいよ！
Oh, sure!
クソガキなところ。
Her bratty side.
なんでも許したくなっちゃうよね。
It makes you want to forgive anything.
それいい所なのか、クソガキ？
Is being a brat a good thing?
一周回っていい所だよね。
It's a good point in a roundabout way.
あとなんか、美味しいものとか貰った時に、「は！嬉しい！」
Also, like when she gets something delicious, she goes, "Ha! I'm so happy!"
めちゃくちゃピュアだよね。
She's so incredibly pure.
全身で震えて喜んでるところ。
The way she trembles with joy all over.
確かに。しかも残さず食べてくれるでござるよな、ちゃんとね。
True. And she finishes everything without leaving any leftovers, doesn't she?
ねえ。可愛い。可愛い。
Yeah. Cute. Cute.
お子様だけどね。
Even though she's like a child.
いろはちゃんは？
What about you, Iroha-chan?
え、でもなんか、ラプラス様って、めちゃくちゃ毒吐くけど...
Well, La+ says some pretty harsh things, but...
最後はちゃんと「ごめんな、今日言い過ぎた」みたいな感じでフォローしてくれる...
In the end, she properly follows up with something like, "Sorry, I said too much today."
大丈夫だろう。裏で風真のなんか色々バラしてるから今日お返しでござる。
It'll be fine. Since she's revealed various things about me behind the scenes, today is my payback.
あとすごい4人のこと見てくれない？
Also, doesn't she look out for the four of us a lot?
あ、そうね。確かに。
Ah, right. Definitely.
なんか、好きなのかなって勘違いすることあるよね。
Sometimes I misunderstand and think, "Wait, does she like us?"
いや、好きなんだよ、きっと。
No, she definitely likes us.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
あれ、好きか？ファンか？みたいな気持ちになることない？
Doesn't it make you feel like, "Wait, does she like us? Is she a fan?"
こよりのこと好きだよね。
She likes Koyori, doesn't she?
確かに。あ、こよりだけだったか。
True. Ah, it was just Koyori.
えへー。あと何だろう？意外に...あ、線引かれたわ。
Hehe. What else? Surprisingly... Ah, she drew a line.
やでも確かに。なんかラプラスのいい所ってさ、意外とみんなのこと大好きだよね。
But it's true. One of La+'s good points is that she surprisingly loves everyone.
もこもこ配信見てるし。
She watches the moko-moko streams.
そうそう。ウフフフ。確かに。心に来るからね。
Right, right. Hahaha. Definitely. It really hits home.
ガチじゃん。
She's serious.
早く体調治ってほしいな。
I hope she gets better soon.
ねえ。マジで。
Yeah. Seriously.
早く元気になれ。元気になれ、お薬飲め。なれ！
Get well soon. Get well, take your medicine. Get well!
お薬して！ホットにして！暖かくして！
Use your medicine! Keep it hot! Stay warm!
好きなラプラス！
We love La+!
しょうがないから好きだよ。
We love her because we can't help it.
大好きだよ！
We love you!
というわけで、アジトに戻ってまいりました！
And so, we've returned to the hideout!
ただいまー！
We're home!
やー、どうだった？
So, how was it?
え、疲れたよ。
Man, I'm tired.
あんなに体力使うと思わなかった。
I didn't think it would take that much energy.
まさかシャトルランすると思わなかった。
I never thought we'd be doing a shuttle run.
え、でも楽しかったね。
But it was fun, wasn't it?
楽しかったー！
It was fun!
ということで目標も達成したということで、ここで告知をさせていただきましょう。
So, since we achieved our goal, let's make some announcements here.
はい、はーい！
Yes, yes!
え？あ、待って。後ろになんか貼ってない？あれ？これこれこれ。
Eh? Ah, wait. Isn't there something posted in the back? Oh? This, this, this.
本当だ。なんかある。これはもしカして？
It's true. There's something there. Could this be?
あ！これ、アニメイト？
Ah! Is this Animate?
そう、アニメイトフェアが実施中でございます。もうみんなアニメイトさんには行ったかな？
Yes, the Animate Fair is currently underway. Has everyone already gone to Animate?
行ったかね？行ったかね？
Have you gone? Have you gone?
ということでね、あのもうゲットした人も、まだこれからだよっていう方もね
So, for those who already got it and those who are about to...
期間までにまたアニメイトに行って頂ければなと思います
I hope you'll head to Animate again before the period ends.
行けない方もね通販ありますからね
There's also mail order for those who can't go.
ぜひチェックしてください
Please check it out.
全外ボイスもあるからね、聴いてね
There's also "Zengai Voice", so please listen.
はい。さらにホロクサーのみんなにお知らせでございます
Yes. Furthermore, we have an announcement for all HoloXers.
ということでホロックス一周年記念グッズがこの後21時に発売決定いたしましたー！
So, the HoloX 1st Anniversary goods will go on sale at 21:00 today!
ということで気になるグッズはこちら、ドン！
So, here are the goods you're interested in, bam!
今回はホロクサー専用のですね、グッズを用意させて頂きました
This time, we've prepared goods exclusively for HoloXers.
ということで一つ目はこちら、ドン！
So, first is this, bam!
はい、めちゃくちゃオシャレ、ホロクサー専用パーカーになっております
Yes, a very stylish, HoloXer-only hoodie.
ということで普通に着れるのはもちろんなんですけども
So, of course you can wear it normally, but...
チャックを閉めれば真のホロクサーとしての姿が見れるらしいです
Apparently, if you zip it up, you can see your true form as a HoloXer.
これね、この子をホロックスでライブとかやった時にね、みんなで着てくれたら嬉しいなと思っております
Well, I'd be happy if everyone wore this when we do lives at HoloX.
そしてそして、パーカーも良いんだけど二つ目がこちら、ドン！
And, and, the hoodie is good, but here's the second one, bam!
お、なんだこれ？
Oh, what's this?
ブラックカード？クレジットカード？
Black card? Credit card?
はい、そうこれがねホロクサーの証明書ということで
Yes, so this is the HoloXer certificate.
ホロクサーだけが持てるホロクサー証明書がなんと今回グッズとなります！
The HoloXer certificate that only HoloXers can have is now a merchandise!
財布の中に入れてたら、あれあの人ブラックカード？
If you have it in your wallet, people will think, "Wait, is that a black card?"
ホロクサーです
I'm a HoloXer.
ということで我こそはホロクサーという方は概要欄に記載しております
So, for those who consider themselves HoloXers, it's in the description.
URLからぜひぜひ購入してみてください
Please purchase it from the URL.
購入できるのは21時からになりますのでご注意ください
Please note that it will be available for purchase starting at 21:00.
ということで先日ね、私たちもアイドル衣装お披露目いたしましたし
So, we also unveiled our idol costumes the other day,
この後はねみんな揃ってアイドル衣装を着てライブパートでございます！
and after this, we'll all be wearing them for the live performance part!
ライブはね、事前に収録したものになりますから
The live performance was pre-recorded,
ラプラスも出演しております！
so Laplus is also performing!
プラスメイトのみんなもお待たせしましたでござる。楽しんでください
Plusmates, sorry to keep you waiting. Please enjoy.
それじゃあみんな盛り上がる準備は出来てるかね？
So, is everyone ready to get hyped?
それじゃあせーのでいきませんか。せーの、どうぞー！
Then, shall we go on three? One, two, here you go!
目合わせ始まる死の定め
Eyes meet, the fate of death begins
不足したままの意思疎通
Communication remains insufficient
意味なし勝負さ満足で
A meaningless contest, satisfied
影の見本市
A trade fair of shadows
空ろに飾りし満場
Hollowly adorned, the whole house
凸凹に振りかざした詭弁
Sophistry brandished unevenly
ギシギシと鋼鉄つかれて
Screeching, steel is exhausted
貼り付けられた顔がひび割れてゆく
The pasted face is cracking
完膚なきまでに潰れた
Crushed completely
この挽回手は
This recovery hand
刻まれた詩は擦り減る靴の外
The engraved poem is outside the worn-out shoes
正、答えを
Correct, the answer
至上主義アドトラック
Supremacist Adtrack
Shijou Shugi Ad-Truck
四六時中駆け回る
Running around 24/7
依然使い捨ての
Still disposable
消耗品だと
consumables
勝負は金だと
It's all about the win
あっと言う間になるなよ
Don't let it end in a flash
ぱっと打ち上げてやれよ
Let it burst and fly high
夜を飲み込む星の花
Flowers of stars that swallow the night
まだ罪に積み重ね
Still piling up sin
積み重ね
upon sin
束ねていく
Bundling up
祈り丸め
prayers, rolling them up
投げ放つ
and throwing them out
最高美の顧客今日も
The most beautiful client today as well
手練れ慣れた駆け引きさぁいざ
With skilled tactics, now come on
息詰まる盛衰天上に
To the suffocating rise and fall
窮地の袋小路
in a desperate dead end
雨にも負けず
Unbeaten by the rain
風にも負けず
Unbeaten by the wind
悟り開いて欲する常識
Attaining enlightenment, desiring common sense
軋みを増した白衣のまま
Remaining in a creaking lab coat
快感の果てへと引き連れてゆく
I'll take you to the ends of pleasure
変わり映えしないチンプな
If it's just a cheap,
悪夢なら捨てちまえ
unchanging nightmare, throw it away
弾け飛ぶスリル抜ける古傷
Thrills bursting, old wounds fading
鳴呼 正解を
Ah, give me the answer
至上主義アドトラックで
With the Shijou Shugi Ad-Truck
唯一無二に打ち下げる
Bringing down a one-of-a-kind result
依然逆立ちの太陽は金だと
That the upside-down sun is still gold
お見舞いに見ておけよ
Take a look as a greeting
ぱっと仕掛けてやれば
If you set it off in a flash
夜になだれる星の花
Flowers of stars cascading through the night
また一つ
Another one,
呼び合わせいく
summoning them together
祈り横へ
Letting the prayers
滑らせる
slide over
そうさずっと僕らの軌跡が
That's right, our trajectory will always
途切れないように歌うんだ
We sing so that it never breaks
もっと高く大きな声で
Higher and with a louder voice
Prism Melody
聞こえてた
I could hear it,
何かが
something,
始まる合図
the signal that something's beginning
集まって
Gathering together,
気付けば
before we knew it,
鼓動奏でて
our heartbeats were playing a melody
夢に見る
Just dreaming about it
だけじゃもう
isn't enough
足りないでしょ
anymore, right?
君を待ってる
There's a world out there
世界があるよ
waiting for you
楽しい予感にほら
Look, with this fun premonition,
飛び乗っちゃいたい
I want to jump right in
ときめきは止められないから
Because I can't stop this heartbeat
走ろう
Let's run
連れていくよ
I'll take you away
光の真ん中
to the center of the light
夢の先へ
beyond our dreams
はばたける
The courage to spread your wings
勇気は君の願い
comes from your wish
みんなでつないだ
This miracle that we all
この奇跡が
connected together
途切れないように歌うんだ
We sing so that it never breaks
もっと高く大きな声で
Higher and with a louder voice
...場所があったんだ
...there was a place.
淀みない道行く 僕らの旅
Our journey on an untroubled path
願いだけが 道しるべだよ
Our wishes are our only guide
夢の色が変わっても 変わらないメロディ
Even if the colors of our dreams change, the melody stays the same
君のために 僕らのために 歌おう
For you, for us, let's sing
そうさ きっと 僕らの軌跡は 終わらないよ
That's right, surely our trajectory will never end
涙さえきっかけに変えて行こう
Let's turn even our tears into a catalyst and move forward
信じてくれる仲間と一緒に どこへだって飛び出して行こう
Together with friends who believe in us, let's fly out anywhere
もっと遠く 空を超えて
Further away, beyond the sky
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬ君に
To our future selves, and to you whom we've yet to see
伝えたいことたくさんあるんだ
There's so much I want to tell you
迎えたい今は 当たり前じゃない
The present we want to welcome is not something to be taken for granted
翼を広げたいま 飛ぼう
Now that we've spread our wings, let's fly
TAKE MY HAND!! 連れて行くよ 光の真ん中
TAKE MY HAND!! I'll take you to the center of the light
夢の先へ羽ばたける 勇気は君の願い
The courage to flap our wings toward the dream's end is your wish
みんなで繋いだこの軌跡が 途切れないように歌うんだ
I'll sing so that this trajectory we've connected together won't be broken
もっと響く大きな声で
With a louder voice that resonates even more
僕らの未来の風 どこまでも響け Prism Melody
Let our future's wind resonate forever, Prism Melody
おや？おや？おや？おや？
Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh?
ということで、至上主義アドトラック、Prism Melody 2曲聴いていただきましたが、皆さんいかがでしたかー？
So, you've heard "Shijoshugi Adtrack" and "Prism Melody". How was it, everyone?
いかがでしたかー？
How was it?
お、楽しんでくれてるみたいだね。
Oh, it looks like you're enjoying it.
いやあ、よかったでござるなー。
Well, that's good to hear.
4人で？
The four of us?
アイドル衣装だー！アイドル衣装だー！イエーイ！
Idol outfits! Idol outfits! Yay!
1周まわっちゃお、1周まわっちゃお、1周まわっちゃお、1周まわっちゃお。はい。はい。
Let's do a spin, let's do a spin, let's do a spin, let's do a spin. Yes. Yes.
いや、かわいい。
Man, so cute.
ね。
Right.
いやさ、並ぶとかわいい。
I mean, standing together like this is cute.
ね、かわいい。
Yeah, cute.
ラプラスは今いないんだけど、そう、3種類のうちの2種類...
La+ isn't here right now, but yeah, two out of the three types...
そうだね。そうだね。
That's right. That's right.
3、2だったんだよね。
It was a 3-2 split, right?
ね、こういうことか。
I see, so that's how it is.
La+、La+、La+、La+...
La+, La+, La+, La+...
そう、La+と、いろはと私が、この、ね、袖付きのタイプだね。
Right, La+, Iroha, and I have this, you know, sleeved type.
なんかよかった。そして、こよりのこと好きすぎて一緒の、真似しちゃった、真似しちゃった、真似しちゃった...
It was nice. And I like Koyori so much I copied her, copied her, copied her...
はーい！はーい！はーい！はーい！
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
もう、改心、改心、改心。
Geez, reform yourself already.
ということで、すごいバランスがよかったね。
Anyway, the balance was really good.
うん。
Yeah.
ということで、曲どうだった？聴いてみて、いや、歌ってみて。
So, how was the song? Listening to it, I mean, singing it.
えの、ダンス頑張ったよね！
Um, we worked hard on the dance!
頑張った！みんなですっごい頑張った！めっちゃ練習したから、みんなでさ、合わせたのがさ、本当に...
We did! We all worked really hard! We practiced so much, and getting together like this was really...
1日だけだったんだよね！
It was only for one day!
そうです！1日なんだよね！
That's right! Just one day!
いや、頑張った。
Man, we worked hard.
ね、我々頑張った。憧れの、ね、先輩たちの、ね、曲を歌って踊ることができましたね。
Yeah, we worked hard. We were able to sing and dance to our admired seniors' song.
はい。何度も見てください！
Yes. Please watch it many times!
ね、お願いします。
Yes, please.
かっこいい曲と、あとね、かわいいもアイドルっていう曲をね、私たち歌ったの初めてだから。
It's our first time singing a cool song and then a cute idol-like song, so...
そうだよね。本当そうだよね。
That's true. It really is.
ねー。
Yeah.
もう、本当にホロライブの一員にみんなでなれたんじゃないかなと、思います！
I think we've all finally truly become members of Hololive!
そしてさらに！
And furthermore!
そして？
And?
今ね、みんなすごいお待ちかねの、最後は...
Now, the moment you've all been waiting for, the finale is...
きちゃう？きちゃう？
Is it coming? Is it coming?
我々の、初めてのユニット曲を披露しまーす！
We're going to perform our very first unit song!
イエーイ！やったー！
Yay! Alright!
ということで、もう、早速聴いてもらおうか。
So, let's have everyone listen to it right away.
はい。いこう。
Yes. Let's go.
ということで、みんなで曲紹介いこう！
Alright, let's all introduce the song!
行くよ、準備はいいか？
Let's go, are you ready?
はい！ オッケー！
Yes! Okay!
最後まで盛り上がってってね！
Keep the energy up until the end!
お願いします！
Let's do this!
せーの！
Ready, go!
常夜リペイントー！
Tokonatsu Repaint!
そこに跪け！
Kneel there!
吐いて捨てるような現実を
A reality you'd spit out and throw away
一刀両断叩き切る
Cutting it down with a single stroke
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし子らよ
O children lost in the endless cycle of reincarnation
漆黒の翼で誘おう
I shall invite you with jet-black wings
我らエデンの星を統べる者
We are the rulers of the Star of Eden
秘密結社...
Secret Society...
holoX!!
Now Low? How Low?
どうしようもないこの世界
This world that can't be helped
(どうして欲しい？)
(What do you want me to do?)
Black Out
終末告げる鐘が鳴る
The bell announcing the end rings
ラッパッパッパッパラ
Ra-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-ra
パって踊ろうぜ Tripしようぜ
Let's dance and trip out
陰キャも陽キャも Sing a Song
Innies and outies, let's sing a song
気持ちいいことだけがすべて
Pleasure is everything
堕ちてゆく闇の底へ
Falling to the bottom of the darkness
甘い甘いメロディ
Sweet, sweet melody
ほらどうぞ どうぞ 手の鳴る方へ
Here you go, here you go, towards the clapping hands
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're dyed in darkness
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world
望めばくれてやろう すべて
If you wish, I'll give it all to you
常識 破り捨てろ
Tear up and throw away common sense
くるくる狂い倒せ 火を付けろ
Go round and round in a frenzy, set it on fire
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret
悪のカリスマ 導くぞ民草
Charisma of evil, leading the common people
正義とか知らないし 地鳴らしして誘い
I don't know anything about justice, inviting you with a rumble
マジメに不真面目 弊社の通過儀礼
Seriously unserious, our company's rite of passage
望み求め願い叶え 世界征服♡
Wishing, seeking, fulfilling desires, world domination♡
ラッパッパって歌おうぜ Swingしようぜ
Let's sing 'ra-pa-pa' and swing
退屈な世界へ Bye Bye Bye
Bye bye bye to the boring world
覚めることのない夢を見せる
I'll show you a dream you'll never wake up from
ほら お眠りなさい
Now, go to sleep
もっともっと奥へ
Deeper and deeper
ほらどうぞ どうぞ イキたいんでしょ？
Here you go, here you go, you want to go, right?
もうやめられない
I can't stop anymore
ほら 悪に染まれば
Look, if you're dyed in evil
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world
望むもの与えよう すべて
I'll give you what you want, everything
ルールを書き換えろ
Rewrite the rules
くるくる回し尽くせ 焼き尽くす
Spin it all around, burn it all up
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
すべてのマガイモノへ
To all the phonies
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret
世界を手にしろ holoX 世界を変えてく holoX
Take the world, holoX. Changing the world, holoX.
holoX! holoX!
世界を手にしろ holoX
Take the world, holoX
世界を変えてく holoX
Changing the world, holoX
世界をこの手に holoX
The world in these hands, holoX
心を解き放て
Release your heart
ほらどうぞ どうぞ 身を任せて
Here you go, here you go, surrender yourself
もう逃げられない
You can't escape anymore
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're dyed in darkness
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world
望めばくれてやろう すべて
If you wish, I'll give it all to you
常識 破り捨てろ
Tear up and throw away common sense
くるくる狂い倒せ 火を付けろ
Go round and round in a frenzy, set it on fire
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything
(ラッパッパーラッパッ)
(Ra-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa)
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret
1周年ありがとうな みんなのおかげで
holoXも共に一生を祝うことが出来たのだ
Thank you for the 1st anniversary.
Thanks to everyone, holoX celebrated its birth together.
これからも2年、10年、100年、
応援し続けてくれると嬉しいのだ！
I'd be happy if you continue to support us
for 2, 10, or 100 years!
holoxerのみんな 大大大大大好き
吾輩より ラプラス・ダークネス
I love all the holoxers so, so much.
From Wagahai, La+ Darknesss
1周年ありがとう♡ まだまだ未熟なholoXを
みんなが支えてくれたおかげで
Thank you for the 1st anniversary♡ Thanks to
everyone supporting the still-immature holoX,
今日という1周年をむかえられました!!
2年目ももっともっと愛されるholoXでいたいな...！
we reached this 1st anniversary!! I want holoX
to be even more loved in our second year...!
ずっと好きでいてね♡ 鷹嶺ルイ
holoX 1th ありがとう!!
Please love us forever♡ - Takane Lui
holoX 1st Thank you!!
貴様らと部下達と みんなに大きい感謝だ!!
これからもよろ〜 博衣こより
Big thanks to you guys, my subordinates,
and everyone!! Keep it up from here on~ - Hakui Koyori
ししょー！ 1周年!! いっしょに過ごしてくれて
ありがと〜〜!! これからもずっとずーーーっと
Master! 1st Anniversary!! Thank you for
spending it with me!! Please stay by my side
となりにいてね！！♡ だいすきだよ！！
沙花叉クロヱ
forever and ever!! I love you!!
- Sakamata Chloe
1周年!! やったー！ これからもholoX 5人！
よろしくお願いいたしますでござる 風真いろは
1st Anniversary!! Yay! All 5 of holoX will
keep doing our best! Support us de gozaru. - Kazama Iroha